https://www.aquariumsupplies.ca/aquarium/privacy.php?osCsid=mr5hmbuqckrohdlmucr8uunup2

Aquarium
Air Pumps & Accessories Air Pumps & AccessoriesAir PumpsAir Stones & DiffusersControl & Check ValvesRepair KitsTubing & ConnectorsAquarium Decorations Aquarium DecorationsArtificial DecorationsMopani WoodAquarium Kits Aquarium KitsRed Sea Reefer AccessoriesRed Sea ReefersAquarium Maintenance Aquarium MaintenanceAlgae MagnetsAlgae Scrapers, Pads & CleanersGlovesSiphon & Gravel CleanersSurface SkimmersBooks BooksCatfishCichlidFreshwaterFreshwater AtlasGarden PondGoldfish & KoiMarine & ReefCalcium ReactorsClose OutsCO2 ComponentsControllers & Monitors Controllers & MonitorsMiscellaneous AccessoriesNeptune Apex Neptune ApexApex CablesFluid MonitoringModulesProbesPinPoint-AccessoriesPinPoint-ControllersPinPoint-MonitorsDosing EquipmentEpoxy & GluesFilter Cartridges Filter CartridgesAqua-ClearEclipseEmperorFluval & MarinaLifegardMagnumMarineLand CanisterMarineLand Rite-SizePenn PlaxRena FilStarSicce & SeachemSupremeTetraWhisperFilter Media Filter MediaAbsorbents and ResinsActivated CarbonsAmmonia RemoversBiological MediaCarbon DosingFilter Floss and PadsFilter Socks & Filter Media BagsPhosphate RemoversFilters FiltersCanister FiltersChemical ReactorsInternal FiltersPower FiltersSponge FiltersSumps and RefugiumsFish Foods Fish FoodsAquaForestFeeding DispensersHikariInvertebrateMiscellaneousNew Life SpectrumOmega SeaPond FoodsTetraTwo Little FishiesVitamins and Growth StimulatorsWardleysFish Tank DividersGlass Canopies & HoodsGravel & Substrates Gravel & SubstratesCichlidRockSaltwaterHeaters HeatersMarineLand HeatersTetra HT HeatersLighting LightingAquarium-HoodsBallast-and-SuppliesFansIncandescent-BulbsLED-Lights LED-LightsAI - Aqua IlluminationAquatic LifeEcoTech MarineKessilMarineLandMaxSpectRed SeaReef Brite AccessoriesReef Brite Lumi LiteReef Brite Lumi Lite Duo & PROReef Brite XHO LEDOtherMetal-Halide-BulbsSquare-Pin-PC-LampsStraight-Pin-PC-LampsT5 FixturesT5 Lamps T5 LampsATI T5 LampsD-D POWER PRO T5 LampsMiscellaneous T5 LampsURI T5 LampsZoo-Med T5 LampsT8 LampsTek-Light-AccessoriesVHO-LampsNetsOverflow BoxesPlant Care Plant CareAquatic Plant MaintenanceCO2 ComponentsAPI SupplementsSeaChem FlourishAquaForestPlumbing Parts Plumbing PartsAdaptersBall ValvesBulkheadsCapsCheck ValvesClampsCouplingsCrossesDiverter ValvesElbowsFill ValvesFlexible Ball Socket JointGlass Drill BitsJohn Guest Speed FittingsNipplesPlugsReducer BushingsStrainersTeesTubingUnionsPropagationProtein Skimmers Protein SkimmersHang-OnIn-SumpSkimmer-AccessoriesReplacement Parts Replacement PartsAquaClear PartsBakPak PartsEmperor Filter PartsEshopps PartsLee's PartsMag-Drive-PartsMagnum-Filter-PartsPenguin-Filter-PartsRena FilStar PartsVortex-PartsWhisper PartsTest Kits Test KitsAmmoniaCalciumCopperIodine/IodideMagnesiumMaster/Combined Test KitsNitrate/NitriteORPOxygenpH & Alkalinity/kHPhosphatePotassiumSalinitySilicateStrontiumTDSThermometersTrapsUltraviolet Sterilizers Ultraviolet SterilizersUV SterilizersUV Replacement LampsUV Replacement PartsWater Movement Water MovementPower Heads Power HeadsAI NeroMaxi-Jet Power HeadsNeptune Systems WAVSicce Power HeadsTunze Power HeadsVorTech EcoSmartZooMed Power SweepWater Pumps Water PumpsBlueLine / PanWorldDanner Mag DrivesLifeGard Quiet One PumpsPump AccessoriesPumpsSicce Multi Quiet PumpsSicce Syncra PRO PumpsSicce Syncra PumpsTubingWavemakersWater Purification Water PurificationParts & AccessoriesReplacement FiltersRO & RODI SystemsTFC MembranesWater Treatments Water TreatmentsAlgae-Control-&-Water-ClarifiersBiological-SupplementsCalcium-SupplementsEnvironmental-ConditionersFreshwater-BuffersIodine-AdditivesMagnesium-AdditivesMiscellaneousNet-and-Coral-DipsPotassium AdditivesSalts-&-Marine-MixesSaltwater-BuffersStrontium-AdditivesTrace-ElementsVitamins and Amino AcidsWater-Conditioners
Pond
Air PumpsFilter MediaFiltersFoodsFountain-HeadsHeatersLightingNetsPumpsSealantTest-KitsTubingUltraviolet Sterilizers Ultraviolet SterilizersUV Sterilizers for PondsUV Replacement LampsWater-Treatments
Reptile
BooksCage AccessoriesCrab AccessoriesDecorFeeding AccessoriesFiltersHeating HeatingRock HeatersLightingReptile FoodsReptile Lighting Reptile LightingReplacement Lamps Replacement LampsIncandescentIncandescent SpotsSubstrates SubstratesCarpet & LinersDesertTropicalThermometersWater Accessories
SHOP BY BRAND
JOIN OUR EMAIL LIST Contact Us
OUR OTHER SITES
Direct2YouPondShop.caLike us on FaceBook
×Close
Join our Mailing List to receive NEW Product announcements, advance notice about specials and other hobby related information!
Your Email Address:
Subscribe
Unsubscribe
Close
Send
Home
Catalog
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
In the course of doing business we need to collect certain personal information from our customers. This Privacy Page answers some of our most frequently asked questions about information that we may collect and lets you know exactly why we collect that information.
What personal information do you collect about me?
Depending on the nature of the services we provide to you we may collect any or all of the following information:
Name
Address
Postal Code
Phone Number
Email Address
Payment card number
Payment card expiry date
Purchase history
Customer satisfaction info
Opinions about products and services
Interests and hobbies
When you visit our web site, we also collect:
* information about your computer, including your IP address, the type of operating system and browser you use, and your computer's location
* what pages you visit on our site and what links you click on
How do you use this information?
The main reasons we collect personal information from you are:
To complete a sales transaction
Credit Card verification
Customer service
Delivery services
Warranties and Returns
If it's a necessary part of any of these transactions, we may disclose your information to another company. For example, when you complete a purchase, we pass on your personal information to a credit card processor so we can complete a credit card payment. We also pass on your name and address to a courier company to complete a delivery.
Use of Personal Information for Secondary Reasons
We also may use your personal information for other, secondary reasons, including:
Marketing
Customer relationship management
Contests/Surveys
Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties
Sometimes, we may also share your personal information with other companies, such as suppliers or manufacturers to complete warranty requests, provide additional product information etc.
Continue
Categories Air Pumps & AccessoriesAquarium DecorationsAquarium KitsAquarium MaintenanceBooksCalcium ReactorsClose OutsCO2 ComponentsControllers & MonitorsDosing EquipmentEpoxy & GluesFilter CartridgesFilter MediaFiltersFish FoodsFish Tank DividersGlass Canopies & HoodsGravel & SubstratesHeatersLightingNetsOverflow BoxesPlant CarePlumbing PartsPropagationProtein SkimmersReplacement PartsTest KitsThermometersTrapsUltraviolet SterilizersWater MovementWater PurificationWater Treatments
Manufacturers
Please SelectAmerican-MarineAPI Rena FilstarAqua IlluminationAqua-FitAqua-UltravioletAquaForestAquarium-PharmaceuticalsAquatic LifeBarrons-Educational-SeriesBlueLineBoyd-EnterprisesBubble MagusCaribSeaCerMedia (MarinePure)Cichlid PressCoral FarmerCoralifeCoralVueD-D H20 SaltD-D-The-Aquarium-Solution-LtdDanner Mag-Drive PumpsDanner-ManufacturingDura-PlasticsDVH AquaticE.S.V.EcoTech-MarineEshoppsGulfstream-Tropical-AquariumHagenHanna InstrumentsHikariHM-DigitalInstant OceanISTAJohn-GuestJR-BooksKamoerKent-MarineKessilLee's-AquariumLifegard-AquaticsMarco RocksMarinelandMaxSpectMergusMilwaukee-InstrumentsMiscellaneous-VendorsNeptune-SystemsNew Life SpectrumNorthFinOmega-SeaPenn-PlaxPerfecto-ManufacturingPolyp-LabPythonRed Sea AquariumsRed-Sea-Fish-pHarmReef BriteSalifertSaline-SolutionsSeachem-LaboratoriesSequenceSicceSpectraPureSunlight-SupplyTAAMTetraTFH-PublicationsTunzeTwo-Little-FishiesUV-LightingVitalis (New Era)Vortex-InnerspaceWardleyWEIL-IndustrieanlagenWinona-Concrete-and-PipeZooMed Aquarium Products
Bestsellers 4 in. White Net w/Green Handle5 in. White Net w/Green HandleFloating ThermometerAquaScape Construction Epoxy - Coraline Algae Colour [113.4 g]AquaFit 3 in. White Net w/Green HandleMarineLand Aquarium Sealant --- 100% Clear Silicone [304 mL]6 in. White Net w/Green HandleAquaScape Construction Epoxy - Rock Grey Colour [113.4 g]10 in. White NetMarineLand Aquarium Sealant --- 100% Clear Silicone [82.8 mL]
Join our Mailing List to receive NEW Product announcements, advance notice about specials and other hobby related information!
Your Email Address:
